cinefolks.com 2008-04-20

# Privacy Policy of CineFolks.Com

**CineFolks** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: 

**Information Automatically Logged**   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. 

**Cookies**   
Various methods are employed to gather this data. "Cookies" are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are "small strings of text" that are stored in browsers; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so.   
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. 

**Registration Forms**   
CineFolks does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals, except when individuals provide such information on a voluntary basis in our contests Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Contact information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. **

External Links

**   
This site contains links to other sites. **CineFolks** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse. **  
Children's Guidelines ( Children under 13 ) **   
This site collects and uses personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent. 

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can Contact Us.
